saltworks.us 2017-05-07

# Privacy Policy | SaltWorks®

The SaltWorks privacy and security measures are designed with the highest interest of our clients in mind, so any personal information that you provide to SaltWorks is used for the purpose of personalizing and enhancing your web experience with SaltWorks, and for no other purpose. SaltWorks specific privacy policies are outlined below.

## The Information We Collect

There are three ways that SaltWorks obtains information from you: (1) via registration on the SaltWorks website; (2) from an online purchase; or (3) from any other form of direct purchase from SaltWorks.

## How We Use The Information

The information obtained from registration online is utilized to improve your web experience with SaltWorks by enabling you to obtain a faster checkout for purchases and/or to receive occasional e-mails which provide you with the latest and greatest information regarding SaltWorks and its products.

The information we ask from you when ordering online is your name, address, phone number, credit card number, email address, etc. and is used only to complete the order, to confirm the order and to confirm shipment of the order. You may, upon placement of an order, opt to allow SaltWorks to save the information for a speedier checkout process the next time. This information is then stored only for the purposes of faster checkout and is not used for any other purpose. We do not store your payment information (credit card number, expiration date, etc.) strictly for security reasons.

SaltWorks does not otherwise utilize your personal information in any way and never shares or sells your e-mail address or other personal information to other companies. No information is collected about you unless you apply for registration or purchase products from us. "Cookies" (small bits of text that your web browser software stores on your computer when you visit certain web sites) are used by SaltWorks only to allow you to use SaltWorks web site in the most efficient manner.

## E-Mail

SaltWorks will only send e-mails to you if you ask for them and you can easily unsubscribe at any time you do so choose. SaltWorks has a strict company policy not to flood people with e-mail correspondence, but simply gives you periodic information so you can stay up to date on what SaltWorks is offering. SaltWorks also uses your e-mail address to confirm your order and to confirm shipment of your order and to respond to any inquiries you make on-line. All e-mails you receive will provide you with information as to how to get off the e-mail mailing list if you so desire.

## Children's Privacy

If you are under 18, you may use seasalt.com only with involvement of a parent or guardian. Although SaltWorks does not specifically direct its website to children, SaltWorks strives to provide children with as much customer service as possible without violating their privacy rights. For their protection, SaltWorks asks that anyone 13 years of age or younger not attempt to register with SaltWorks or otherwise provide SaltWorks with any personal information without the consent of a parent or legal guardian.

## Access To Your Personal Information.

SaltWorks will provide you with access to the personal information you provided to SaltWorks by allowing you to view and modify or the information we store related to you. In order to protect your privacy, SaltWorks takes steps to verify your identity before granting you access to the private information or enabling you to make corrections. SaltWorks will accomplish this through the use of passwords and personal data.

## Security

Our website's system is designed to monitor activity and prevent any unauthorized disclosure of credit card numbers or other personal information. In addition, we utilize a licensed system for credit card authorization and fraud detection. We use industry standard SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) encryption to protect the confidentiality of your personal information.

## Updates to Privacy Information

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post a new policy on our Site and change the date at the bottom of the policy. Therefore, we encourage you to check the date of our privacy policy whenever you visit this Site for any updates or changes.

Privacy Policy posted: 2/1/2016

**SaltWorks ®, Inc.**  
16240 Wood-Red Rd NE  
Woodinville, WA 98072  
United States  
Phone: (800) 435-7258
